elephone.hk 2019-04-20

# Privacy Policy-Keep Expecting and Be Surprised

**How we collect your info**

When you register on our site, place an order, or subscribe to our newsletter, you info will be submitted to us, including name, e-mail, mailing address or phone number. Or you can, visit our site anonymously.

**How we use your information?**

Any of the information you submitted may be used in one of the following ways:

• To personalize your browsing experiences  
• To improve customer service   
• To process transactions  
• To inform you of special promotion, survey, activity or other events

**How we protect your information?**

We implement various security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you have allowed it via your settings. This enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools for you in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us directly conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting our customer service at [.](https://support.gearbest.com/)

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, exchange or leak your personal information to outside, but not including trusted third parties who assist us in business as long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

  Copyright © 2019 ELEPHONE. All Rights Reserved.
